mywibes.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy - XtGem.com — Visual mobile site building tool

XTGEM Service Provider aims to ensure the protection of XTGEM website visitors’ and service users’ privacy. This privacy policy is applied only to XTGEM website.

By logging in to XTGEM website and using its services you have to agree with these conditions of privacy policy. If you do not agree with this privacy policy, we kindly ask you not to use XTGEM services and leave the XTGEM website.

**Collection and Use of Information about the User**  
The user logged in to XTGEM website can be identified according to his user name or password. The user who is not logged in may be identified according to the IP address of his network.

XTGEM service user understands and agrees that XTGEM Service Provider receives and collects data about the user each time the user logs in. XTGEM Service Provider automatically receives information of non personal nature identifying each user of XTGEM website: IP address, the operation system of the user‘s computer, type of browser, flow regularities, other similar data and the information on the account created by the user on XTGEM website. This data is used for management, administration of XTGEM website and for the improvement of the quality of the services provided by XTGEM.

XTGEM Service Provider has a right to use information of non personal nature and disclose it to third persons in order to improve the quality of the services provided by XTGEM to its users. IP addresses of users are recorded for a limited period of time for the purposes of safety and observation.

XTGEM service users communicate with each other on XTGEM website without disclosing their e-mail addresses. Full names of users are never disclosed to other XTGEM service users. User names, e-mail addresses and other personal information provided by the users can be used by XTGEM Service Provider only in order to be able to react to the users’ requests, contact them by e-mail, and inform them on the amendments to XTGEM rules or this Privacy Policy.

XTGEM Service Provider obliges not to disclose any personal information of the user to any third persons without the user's permission, except when this information needs to be presented according to the effective legal acts or other cases indicated in this Privacy Policy.

XTGEM service user understands and agrees that the risks related to the submission of personal data are always possible and that such information which XTGEM service user discloses voluntarily on XTGEM website forums, chat rooms, messages, pictures, etc. becomes publicly accessible to all XTGEM service users and can be collected and used by other XTGEM service users who can resend and provide this data on other websites otherwise make them publicly accessible to other third persons and in such a case this data of an XTGEM service user are not stored as personal.

Also the log in name of an XTGEM service user may be shown to other XTGEM service users when the user sends or uploads information on XTGEM website and so other service users who receive this information may contact the user by writing messages or using XTGEM services.

© 2019 xtgem.com
